[theme music playing]
[gunshots]
[gun clicks, fires]
[whoosh, slashing sounds]
[machine gun fire]
[machine gun fire continues]
[single gunshot]
[rapid gunfire]
[echoing blast]
[blade whooshing]
[tense music builds]
[Emilia] Hi, Papa.
Your favorite daughter is back.
And by the way, I've already
gained the Triad's support.
[Lily] Even if it takes us months,
years, or decades,
we'll find that mass grave.
We'll find the victims
and help their surviving families.
[Julio] The only time
they'll see that mass grave
is when their corpses are
on their way down into that pit.
But before that happens,
I want the people of Ardiente to witness
how I'll mete out my punishment
and wrath on Lily and Diego.
[Diego] Be careful.
I wish I could stay by your side
so I could protect you.
But this will help so many.
And once we find that mass grave,
this will be the biggest case
Julio Ardiente will face.
[screaming]
[goon] Who called this meeting?!
-[grunt]
-[gunshot]
[gunshots]
[Jepoy] Anna!
[grunts]
[Marlon] Anna? Anna, wake up.
[Anna] So, you weren't the one
who saved me first.
[Lily] The mass grave
could be around here.
This is where we're headed.
-[gunshots]
-[Lily] Get away from here!
Find Diego and tell him
Julio's men ambushed us.
-I can't just leave you--
-Mom, I'll be right behind you.
[thump]
[Magbanua] Governor, we have Lily Cruz.
[groans]
Diego! The Ardientes have Lily Cruz.
What?
[somber choral music playing]
-[tense music playing]
-[Camia breathes heavily]
[phone ringing]
-[heavy breathing]
-[phone ringing]
Diego…
What?!
[panicked breathing]
They took her?!
Diego!
[panicked breathing]
[tense music playing]
[thuds]
[Magbanua] Go on. Bring her inside.
[tense music playing]
[ominous music playing]
[groans]
[sighs]
[grunts]
[Magbanua] Governor.
[ominous music swells]
[ominous music fades]
Lily Cruz.
Well, Lily…
We meet again.
Aren't you going to try and break free?
Aren't you going to scream?
"Julio, you monster! You're despicable!"
No words?!
[grunts] You know…
There are only two kinds of people
who would do this silent treatment
like you're doing right now.
Those…
who are extremely stupid…
and those…
who are extremely guilty.
Which one are you, Lily Cruz?
-Well?!
-[thump]
-[Magbanua grunts]
-Wake her up.
[grunts]
I don't want her unconscious.
I'm not guilty.
I didn't kill your grandson.
He killed himself
like the damned animal he was.
My grandson turned into that…
because of you!
It's your fault!
You seduced him.
You made him fall in love with you
and toyed with him.
You broke his heart and ruined his life.
That's why, Lily Cruz…
You killed Arnaldo!
-I didn't kill your grandson!
-You killed him!
Is it that hard to accept, Julio?!
He killed himself with his own gun!
Your beloved grandson killed himself
because he couldn't stand
becoming the monster
you turned him into.
Truth is, you're the one
who killed your own grandson!
Enough!
[tense music playing]
You deserved every bit of pain
I inflicted on you
after everything you did to my family!
So, we're right back where we started.
Emilia killed your father.
Then, you killed my grandson!
And so, you got your revenge.
And now, I will get mine.
Have you looked
into a mirror lately, Lily Cruz?
Don't be surprised if you see me
staring back at you.
If you think I'm despicable,
then so are you.
You're standing in the same quagmire
I'm supposed to be standing in right now.
You've become despicable yourself
because you became a murderer
when you killed Arnaldo!
[tense music playing]
[strained voice] Have you ever felt pain?
No, you never felt pain
like I have felt it.
But I will make sure
that you will feel pain…
because I'll make you suffer…
and I'm going to enjoy watching it.
[sniffles]
[sobbing] I will make you suffer
the way I'm suffering right now.
[tense music playing]
Lily Cruz…
What did you say you were again?
"Lily Cruz, I'm made of gold
because I am indestructible"?!
Well, I am going to be the one
to destroy you…
and I will enjoy every minute of it.
This is a promise:
[sniffling]
You will suffer!
[suspenseful music playing]
[tense music playing]
Wow, Stefano. What a surprise.
Why did you invite me here?
Have a seat.
[tense music playing]
I just want to get to know
you better, Emilia.
Thank you.
[wine trickling]
But you know that I'm married, right?
We do.
[scoffs softly]
I was given an important
assignment by the Triad.
I'm looking for a new partner…
who I can trust.
Cheers.
[tense music playing]
[man] Listen up, everyone!
The Governor wants us
to head over to the plaza.
He said they will bring Lily Cruz there
and punish her for murdering our mayor!
Let us show our support for the Ardientes!
We'll be one with the Ardientes!
-Let's support the Ardientes!
-[crowd clamoring]
-Come on!
-Let's go!
[Diego] I won't give up, Lily.
I will save you.
[tense music playing]
You don't have to worry
about anything, Stefano,
least of all, my father.
Just so you know,
he's at my mercy right now,
so no matter what, he'll agree
to the Triad's plans.
If Red Dragon's daughter
really is ferocious,
then we are unstoppable together.
My mama taught me very well.
[tense music playing]
[phone ringing]
-Oh.
-[phone ringing]
Hello?
Emilia…
Get your big behind up here.
[Julio] Yes.
We have her again.
The indestructible Lily Cruz.
But from where I stand…
she doesn't look so indestruct--
[walking canes clatter]
[Julio scoffs]
A little feisty, maybe.
Okay, Papa.
[tense music playing]
[wailing]
[sniffles] Madrigal…
I have never loved anyone
as much as I love you.
[crying]
[sniffles]
I've loved so many men.
I've been with so many men.
[sobbing]
But I've never cried for anyone.
What's holding us back, huh?
What's stopping you from loving me?
Huh?!
I love you, Madrigal.
I love you too, Anna.
What?!
Did you say "Anna"?!
I'm sorry.
Anna?
Anna?!
Huh?
She's the one getting
in the way of our relationship?
I know what I have to do
to get rid of her…
and make you love me.
I know exactly what to do.
[unsettling music playing]
Auntie Camia.
-Jepoy.
-Auntie Camia.
I got your message. What happened?
-Jepoy--
-Where's Lily?
I don't know, either.
But I'm supposed to meet Diego here.
[unsettling music playing]
[car door opens]
-Jepoy! Mom!
-Where's Lily?
Diego, where's Lily? Where's my daughter?
The Ardientes have her.
They're taking her to the plaza.
I'll go save her.
What will they do to Lily?
Mom…
[Emilia] Dad?
-Dad.
-Emilia.
Took you long enough to get back.
So, where is that
indestructible Lily Cruz?
[tense music playing]
You murderer!
-You're a murderer!
-Emilia!
Emilia, calm down.
Emilia, stop it!
Emilia!
Calm down.
You will get your chance.
Tomorrow is the big day.
[tense music playing]
[chuckling]
Relax.
[tense music playing]
No matter what happens,
we'll push through with Lily's plan.
We will reveal everything.
Diego, please save my daughter.
Don't worry.
Even if it means giving up my life,
I'll do it just to save her.
Jepoy, take her back home.
-I'm on it.
-Bye, Mom. Take care.
[car engine starts]
Jepoy, it's time.
We must execute Lily's plans now.
Are we going?
We need to support Diego.
We beat the Ardientes at their own game.
Now, I'm sure those monsters
are mustering their forces
so they can retaliate against us.
But before that happens,
we have to go all out
to ensure their downfall.
What are you planning?
You should stay behind
when we go to Raul's funeral.
What I want you to do
is go to every witness we have
against the Ardientes.
Tell them that now is the time
to face their fears
and come out of hiding.
Because we'll unearth every
horrible thing the Ardientes did
so that the people can finally
exact their revenge on them.
What are you doing here?
Lily has a message for you.
She's about to bring down the Ardientes.
But she needs your help
in order to do that.
We all know that you sold
your soul to those devils.
This is your chance to get it back.
This is your chance to stop living in fear
and start living freely.
Now is the time to atone
for your mistakes.
If we all work together,
there's no doubt that we can
take the Ardientes down.
We can finally give justice
to all their victims.
Can we count on you to help us?
To exact justice from the Ardientes?
[laughing]
Are you joking?!
Are you kidding me?!
It's never going to happen!
The Ardientes have been ruling
over this land for all time.
And you have been selflessly
fighting this war for all your life.
Have you accomplished anything?
You haven't, have you?
[scoffs] So, why should I believe you?
Hmm?
Why should I trust you?
You know that all I want
is justice for my father.
But I'm not going to fall into
your empty promises.
I'm not promising you anything, Natalie.
But I will tell you this:
You'll never get justice for your father
unless we all work together.
We have to help each other
and stand united
against the Ardientes once and for all.
Jepoy…
You want us to join forces
against the Ardientes?
Yes.
And you want me to help Anna and Lily?
You want me to connive
with Anna and Lily?
[laughing]
I feel like I'm talking to a crazy man.
Well, let me remind you.
Anna's the woman that you're crazy for.
And Ivy…
I'm sorry, Lily…
was the woman Arnaldo was crazy for.
So, why would I join forces with you guys
to get what I want?
[chuckles] It makes no sense.
It's never going to happen.
-Natalie, please--
-Not in your wildest dreams!
Natalie, listen to me!
Let's set aside our personal issues.
We all want the same thing,
and that's justice!
The reason why we can't win against them
is that we're all divided!
Let's help each other.
Why don't we join forces?
[slow tense music playing]
Natalie, I'm counting on you
to do the right thing.
Do it…
for your father.
-We need to hurry--
-Jepoy! Ms. Camia!
We heard about what happened to Lily.
We're here to help.
I'll get our witnesses ready.
But the Ardientes will just
fool their supporters again.
We need strong evidence of
the Ardientes' heinous crimes.
-That's right.
-Exactly.
I saw some skeletons
in the woods of San Bartolome.
Let's expose all of
the Ardientes' dastardly deeds.
That may be the only way
for us to save Lily.
[tense music playing]
[Lily] I won't let these monsters win.
As long as I'm still alive,
I'll always have an ace up my sleeve.
I will not go down without a fight.
Let's go.
[suspenseful music playing]
[tense music swells]
[car door closes]
[unsettling music playing]
JUSTICE FOR THE MAYOR
ARREST LILY CRUZ
-Ben!
Where'd you go? Where were you earlier?
Lily Cruz was kidnapped by the Ardientes.
We need to help her.
[stuttering] Why?
I didn't say I would help you
go against the Ardientes.
I didn't promise you guys anything!
What's that?
Mind your own business.
No matter what you do, you will
never defeat the Ardientes
because they have everything:
money and power.
The Ardientes will only kill you
the same way they killed your loved ones.
Hold on.
Weren't you the one who convinced us
to go against the Ardientes?
Huh?
-Where are you going?!
-Hold on!
Don't touch me!
[Edna gasps]
Ben? What's that?!
Where'd you get that money?!
What did you do, Ben?!
Did you tell Julio about our plans?!
Yes! What do you care?!
All that matters in this world is money!
I don't care about your cause.
Ouch!
[Ben groaning in pain]
What's happening to Ben?
I was bitten by a…
-Ben!
-[Ben groaning in pain]
What's happening to him?!
[groans in pain]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Ronald gasps]
Lethal scorpion.
[chuckling]
[chuckles]
For the idiot, Ben.
Does he not know that betrayal
comes with a price?
You three.
The moment the scorpion bites Ben,
take my money back and leave right away.
But before you leave him,
make sure he's dead as a doornail.
Yes, sir.
Do your job, my little pet.
[Ben groaning in pain]
[phone ringing]
Jepoy?
What?
Okay, we're on our way.
-What did he say?
-They found the mass grave.
We need to go there right away.
[tense music playing]
[car door opens]
Roll down your window.
Good evening, sir. This is a checkpoint.
Can you please step out for a second?
[car door opens]
[tense music playing]
Step out of the car!
-[car door opens]
-Step out!
[tense music playing]
[car door opens]
Hold on.
Can you take off your cap?
Take off your cap!
It's Diego!
[grunts]
Hey! Stop right there!
[Lily grunts]
[Lily groaning in pain]
Diego… Diego…
[action music playing]
[grunts]
Don't worry, Lily.
We're already looking
for your husband Diego.
Get up!
Try to fight back!
[gunshots]
Hurry!
-Hey! Stop!
-[gunshot]
Very soon…
you will be together.
[groaning]
Sleep, my dear. You need your rest.
[snickers]
[melodramatic music playing]
[indistinct shouting]
[shouting continues]
It's over, Lily.
[soft piano music playing]
[music swells]
[music fades]
[indistinct shouting]
[man] You killed our mayor!
-She should be killed!
-Kill her!
[woman] You killed the mayor!
[woman] Traitor! Kill her!
[indistinct shouting continues]
JUSTICE FOR MAYOR ARNALDO
-You're scum!
-Monster!
Look at her! She's a criminal!
[woman] Criminal!
-You're a murderer!
-Scum!
Murderer!
You killed our mayor!
That woman has no soul!
Criminal! Murderer!
You're the scum of this town!
-You deserve to be punished!
-Right?! Punish the criminal!
[indistinct shouting]
-Scum!
-You should be killed!
-Murderer! Criminal!
-You're scum!
[indistinct shouting continues]
-Kill her!
-Yeah!
[woman] Monster!
[indistinct shouting continues]
[cheers and applause]
[crowd chanting] Long live, Ardiente!
[chanting continues]
[cheers and applause]
-Long live, Ardiente!
Everyone!
[shutter clicks]
Behold…
the cancer afflicting this town…
Lily Cruz!
[woman] Death penalty for Lily Cruz!
She killed the mayor!
[man] She killed the mayor! Death penalty!
-You're a murderer!
-Murderer!
-Punish her!
-Hang her!
-Punish the murderer!
-Kill her!
-Hang her upside down!
-Hang her!
-You're a criminal!
-Scum!
-Criminal!
-Punish her!
-You're a criminal!
-Punish that woman!
[Julio] Send her away.
I'll avenge the mayor!
You monster! You killed the mayor!
[indistinct shouting continues]
[man] Punish her! Hang her!
[Julio] Lily Cruz…
This is how you will meet your end.
[tense music playing]
You know, my sons and daughters…
my dearest constituents…
Our town lived in peace
until this woman came here.
We welcomed her to our town
with open arms.
My family even welcomed her
into our very own house.
We had no idea that this traitor
had an evil plan in mind:
To kill your beloved Mayor Arnaldo.
Lily Cruz…
betrayed us all.
-Kill her!
-Kill that woman!
The traitor of Poblacion Ardiente!
-Scum!
[indistinct shouting]
[woman] How could you do that?!
You killed an innocent man!
What do you want, Emilia?
What do you want me to do?
-Admit that you killed my son!
-[woman] She did!
-[Emilia] Right, everyone?!
-[crowd] Yeah!
[Emilia] Confess to everyone who's here,
and then, get down on your knees.
-[man] That's right!
-[woman] Kneel!
[softly] Because if you don't,
I will bring Diego here and parade him
before all these people, just like you.
So, kneel!
-[man] Kneel, you monster!
-[woman] Kneel!
You heard my daughter, woman!
Kneel!
[suspenseful music playing]
[Lily] To save Diego…
To rekindle the hope that will
end the people's suffering…
I'll do it.
-[man] Kneel, now!
-[woman] Kneel down!
You heard them, right?
I said, kneel!
[unsettling music swells]
[crowd cheers and applauds]
[indistinct shouting]
[man] Kill her!
[cheers and applause]
-Kill that woman!
-Kill her!
[cheers and applause]
[indistinct shouting]
[Julio] Look at me!
Look at me! Huh?!
[cheers and applause]
[indistinct shouting]
-Long live, Ardiente!
[chanting] Long live, Ardiente!
[crowd chanting] Hang her!
-You murderer!
-Murderer!
[indistinct shouting]
Go on!
[sobbing]
Lily! Lily…
Lily! Get out of my way!
-Where are you going?!
-Out of my way! Lily!
Get out of my way! You monsters!
Why are you hurting my daughter?!
[Camia] Get out of my way, you monsters!
Don't…
-Stop right there!
-Don't you dare hurt her!
[Camia sobbing]
-Mom?
-Let go of me!
-Mom.
-You monsters!
Let her go, you monsters!
Mom…
[sobs] Lily…
[Camia sobbing]
-She's innocent.
-Mom… Mom!
-[Camia crying]
-Mom…
[Emilia] How nice of your mother
to join us.
[chuckles] What a sweet reunion.
[Camia crying] Lily…
Lily! Please let her go.
Emilia…
Not my mother. Hurt me instead.
[sobbing] I'm begging you.
Emilia.
-[sobbing] She's innocent!
-Mom…
Mom.
-Lily!
-Stay.
[melodramatic music playing]
[Lily] Emilia!
-Well?!
-Emilia!
This isn't enough
for what you did to my son.
-Since you made him suffer,
-[Lily] Don't, Emilia.
-I'll make you suffer too!
-Emilia! Mom!
Emilia! Don't!
[crying]
-I'm begging you…
-Stop this! Hurt me instead!
[somber choral music playing]
Marlon, Jepoy!
[gun clicks]
Anna, careful.
[somber choral music playing]
Ronald, what if my parents are down there?
[Edna sobbing]
Mom?
Dad?
[Edna sobbing]
The show is not over yet, wonder girl!
-Mom.
-I'm begging you.
Just stop this, you monsters!
[ominous music playing]
Lily…
[melodramatic music playing]
We are going for a walk.
I'm going to escort you to hell!
-Sounds good, everyone?
-Yes! For the mayor!
[indistinct shouting]
We're going to call this:
"The March of Sinners".
[Camia] My daughter
didn't do anything wrong!
She's innocent!
You can't let the Ardientes
abuse their power!
[sobs] You can't!
Magbanua!
Where is it?
Move!
Do you see this?!
I AM A MURDERER
I KILLED YOUR MAYOR
Put this around that woman's neck!
-Mom…
-[Camia sobbing]
[indistinct shouting]
[Emilia slowly reading] "I am a murderer".
I'M A MURDERER
I KILLED YOUR MAYOR
Fits perfectly, right? All right then!
Start marching!
This is what criminals like you deserve.
-Hurry up! Move!
-You deserve it!
[Camia] Stop this!
-You killed the mayor!
-She's a murderer!
[somber music playing]
What's wrong with you all?!
How could you?!
My daughter sacrificed
so much for all of you!
Are you all blind?! Open your eyes!
Liars! Burn in hell!
She's nothing but a murderer!
Liar! Stop spreading lies
about the Ardientes!
Prove yourselves first!
-You're all blind!
-Liar! Liar!
[indistinct shouting]
[woman] Kill her!
[whip cracking]
-Kill her!
-[whip cracking]
[man] You get what you deserve!
[whip cracking]
[indistinct shouting]
[ominous music playing]
[whip cracking]
-[whip cracking]
-[woman] No! Don't hurt Lily!
-Take us instead!
-Have mercy on her!
-Let Lily go! I beg you!
-You want to? Come here then!
-Have mercy on her!
-Arrest them!
-Please!
-We beg you!
The Ardientes are the real murderers here!
-You're the real crooks!
-Stop this, please!
Please don't hurt Lily Cruz!
She's innocent!
[whip cracking]
-[whip cracking]
-[woman] Stop it, please!
Have mercy on her! Please stop!
[whip cracking]
[melodramatic music playing]
[Jepoy] Now is the time for change!
-Down with the Ardientes!
[Magbanua] Standing order
from the Governor:
when the primary Tango arrives,
shoot to kill.
[Julio] Blood will be paid with blood.
-[crowd shouting]
-Stop this!
[Diego] Thank you for gathering
the townspeople today!
Now, they can see just how tainted
your souls really are!
Arrest them! Arrest them all!
-[gunshot]
-[Emilia] Papa!
-[gunshots]
-[people screaming]
[Julio] You ruined my family!
You ruined the Ardientes!
This is your fault!
[stool clatters]
[theme music playing]